Today is Lake Yamanakako in2024
I would like to take a solo picture town
Yay!
We are going to send you a vlog with mysterious members!
Emachi and Yamanakako Vlog will start!
Emachi at the Rango-zaka service area
Emachi with the principal
We got tsukune (sticky rice cake)!
Munching!
Delicious!
Taste this too!
This one too!
Mt. Fuji is in sight!
Cute swans on the lake!
I wonder if I can open a bottle of Ramune.
I could open it!
The main dish was a sword!
Be careful, it's very hot!
How do you like it?
Mochi Mochi!
I'll have some horse sashimi, too
Delicious!
Fuji and Pinyonpyon Emachi
Smoothies for balance!
But you should come to eat!
Delicious and refreshing!
What?
Now that I've got the bug. Now that the bug is on
Face
It's okay, they're gone.
I went there because my owner really wanted to be
as expected, I couldn't fly like that
Pimpin' and Pimpin' and Pimpin' and Pimpin'
Fuji has gone
Emachi running around the principal
The radio waves are so bad!
Fuji is beautiful
constitu
jr
Kumagaya
Ah, Emachi-Machi Fuji!
Good acting.
Pimpin Emachi
Landing
Emachi from the slide
You made me sad.
I used to get chafed all the time
Now it hurts, it hurts
The bars and Emachi
Here we go.
Well done!
I've played so much, I'm at the end of my strength
I'm so tired!
I'd like to go back to Tokyo soon.
Please come and visit us.
Thank you for watching!